Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
Please stop crying.
I'm begging you.
I don't know what else to do.
My boobs are empty.
Do you want lasagna?
It's okay, it's okay.
Shh...
What have we done?
(Penny:)What... what's all this?
(Leonard:)Well, it sounded like
you were having a rough day,
(Leonard:)so I wanted you to come home
to something nice.
(Penny:)Oh, that is so thoughtful.
(Leonard:)Hey, do you remember when
we went wine tasting
(Leonard:)in Santa Barbara
and you said
that was the best
rosé you'd ever had?
(Penny:)Yeah, I remember
us driving up there,
(Penny:)going to the winery and...
(Penny:)that's it.
(Leonard:)And this wine is why.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Penny:)Hey, what smells so good?